Guide to the Harold F. Gosnell Papers 1886-1997
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Writings
  - Subseries 1: Books
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Proofs, Typescripts, Illustrations, Corrections, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Publication Notes, undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Illustrations, Table of Contents, Preface, undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Legal documents, 1950s-1970s (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Promotion, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Reviews, 1980-1983 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript, Chapters 1-10, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript, Chapters 11-20, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Typescript, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Typescript, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Typescript, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey From Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey from Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript of Chapters 3-5, Correspondence, Research, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey from Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript of Chapters 6-13, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey from Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript of Chapters 14-20, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey from Lamar to the White House -- Manuscript and Typescript, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Harry S. Truman's Journey from Lamar to the White House -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Why Europe Votes -- Publisher List and Contracts, 1930 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Articles and Other Writings
    - "Analysis of 1932 Presidential Vote in Chicago," 1935 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Book reviews, 1930s-1980s (Box 53, Folder 2-10)
    - "British Royal Commissions of Inquiry," 1934 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - "Characteristics of the Non-Naturalized,"1929 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - "The Chicago Black Belt as Political Battleground," 1933 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Chicago elections, assimilation and association, 1921-1941 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - "The Chicago Election," 1927 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - "Citizenship as a Requirement for Voting," undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Co-authored articles, 1920s-1950s (Box 54, Folder 4-5)
    - Colliers Encyclopedia, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - "A Critique of Polling Methods," with Sebastian DeGrazia, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - "The Definition of Representation," 1945 (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
    - "Democracy and Values," undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - The Dictionary of American History, various entries, 1939 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - "Disfranchisement," undated (Box 54, Folder 12-13)
    - "Does Campaigning Make a Difference?" undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Encyclopedia Americana, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1957-1969, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 3-5)
    - "Fighting Corruption in Chicago," circa 1939 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - "Filipinos Hold Free Election,"1954 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Forthal, Sonya, book foreword, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - "The German Referendum on Princes' Policy," 1927 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - "How Accurate Were the Polls?" 1937 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - "How the Negroes Vote In Chicago," 1933 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Howard University Magazine and various articles, 1941-1964 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - "Indonesians Go to the Polls," 1958 (Box 55, Folder 13-14)
    - "Instruction and Research," 1949 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - International Encyclopedia of Statistics, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - "An Interpretation of the Philippine Election of 1953," 1954 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - "An Irish Free state Senate Election," 1926 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - "A List System With Single Candidate Preference," 1939 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - "Methods of Increasing Popular Participation in Elections," 1925 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - "Mobilizing the Electorate," 1948 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - "The Negro Vote in Northern Cities," 1941 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - "The Negro as a Voter and an Officeholder," 1963 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - "A New Method for Counting Proportional Representation Ballots," 1925 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - "News and Notes from the American Political Science Review," 1926 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - "The 1958 Elections in the Sudan," 1958 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - "The Obsolescence of Books in College Libraries," undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - "Obstacles to Domestic Pamphleteering by OWI in World War II," 1946 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - "A Parliamentary By-Election in Paris," 1926 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - "Participation in the Forthcoming Elections," 1952 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - "Political Meetings in Chicago's Black Belt," 1934 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - "Political Parties in the Modern World," undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - "Politics and Numbers," circa 1934 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - "Policy Agencies," 1936 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - "Popular Law Making in the United States," 1924-1940 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - "Popular Law Making in the United States," 1924-1940 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
    - "Popular Participation in Swiss National Council Elections," 1930 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - "Professional Associations," with Margaret J. Schmidt, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - "Professional Organizations as Pressure Groups," 1935 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - "Progressive Politics: Wisconsin," with Morris H. Cohen, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - "Proportional Representation," 1939 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - "Proportional Representation: Its Operation in Cincinnati," undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - "Public Opinion Research in Government," with Moyca C. David, 1949 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - "Relation of Economic and Social Conditions of Voting Behaviour in Iowa, 1924-1936," 1941 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - "Short-wave Radio Listening in the Chicago Area," with Alfred DeGrazia), undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Social Science Research Council Commissions of Inquiry, 1930s-1940s (Box 57, Folder 12-13)
    - "Some Practical Applications of Psychology in Government," 1921 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - "Statisticians and Political Scientists," 1933 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - "Symbols of National Solidarity," 1941 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - "Technique of Measurement," 1929 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - "Theories of Representation," undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - "Thomas C. Platt, Political Manager," 1923 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - "Die Volksbeteiligung bei den englischen Wahlen," undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - "The Vote Problem in Europe," 1926 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - "Voting," undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - World Book Encyclopedia, 1947-1950 (Box 58, Folder 8-21)
  - Subseries 3: Writings by Others
    - "American Political Science Review," 1924, 1925, 1926, 1932, 1944, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 1-7)
    - Ames, Edward Scribner, "Liberalism in Religion," 1936 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, 1923 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Bean, Louis H., Ballot Behaviour, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Betts, Charles, "The Naked Truth,"1921 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Blydenburgh, John Carl, Two Attempts to Measure the Effects of Precinct Level Campaigning, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Bridge, Horace J., "Richard Wright's 'Native Son': The Acid Test of Americana," 1940 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Bunche, Ralph, "The Political Status of the Negro," undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Castell, Alberto, "Public Opinion Research in Latin America," 1983 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Hymen and Merriam, C.E., "Leadership," 1934 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Cox, Garfield V., "Some Distinguishing Characteristics of the Current Recovery," 1936 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - DeGrazia, Alfred J., suffrage, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 11-14)
    - DeGrazia, Alfred J., suffrage, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - Director, Herman B., "The Effect of the Short Ballot Movement," 1937 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Douglas, Paul H., "Three Saints in Politics," 1971 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Douglas, Paul H., "The Filibuster," 1957 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Durkheim, Emile, "Selected Readings of Anomie," 1947 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Galloway, George, "Modernizing Congress," undate (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - George, Alex, "An Analysis of Propaganda in German Nazi 9 Election- Plebiscites," undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - German publications, 1920s-1930s (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Gideonese, Harry, "Integration of the Social Sciences and the Quest for Certainty," 1936 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Goldman, Ralph M., presidential voting, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 11-12)
    - Graves, W. Brooke, "The Future of the American States," 1936 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Hardt, John p., "Soviet Defense Expenditures and the US Defense Debate," 1976-1977 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Head, William P., "Truman's China Policy," 1983 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - History and politics, 1920s-1940s (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - International Affairs: A Study Handbook, circa 1920s (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - "International Journal of Ethics," 1929, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 3-4)
    - "James Waller," undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Jernegan, Marcus, "Productivity of Doctors of Philosophy in History," 1927 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Claudius O., Carter Henry Harrison I, 1928 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Jones, "Party Voting in the English House of Commons," undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - "Journal of the American Statistical Association," 1936 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - "Journal of Business of the University of Chicago," 1934 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Folders1-2: "Journal of Political Economy," 1927,1944 (Box 63)
    - Kousoulas, D., "On Government," circa 1966 (Box 63, Folder 3-5)
    - Landau, Martin, "Sociology and the Study of Formal Organization," 1965 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Lasswell, Harold D., "Chicago's Old First Ward: A Case Study in Political Behaviour," 1923 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Leamer, Lawrence E., Economic Conditions and Presidential Elections," circa 1940s (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Merriam, Charles E., "Public Administration and Political Theory," 1940 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Merriam, Charles E., "Some Social Implications of Interventions," undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Morgenthau, Hans, "National Socialist Doctrine of World Organization," 1941 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - "National Municipal Review," 1930 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - "On the Developed and the Developing,"1965 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Palmer, Vivien, "The Social Backgrounds of Chicago's Local Communities," undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - "Parliaments and Stable Government," 1928 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Pollock, James, "The SAAR Plebiscite," 1935 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Pritchett, Henry S., "The Social Philosophy of Pensions," 1930 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Public policy, 1920s-1940s (Box 63, Folder 18-19)
    - Public policy, 1920s-1940s (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
    - "Rethinking Chicago," undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Rice, Stuart A., "Why I Became a Sociologist," 1969 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Rubin, Leslie and Neville, "This is Apartheid," 1965 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Shepard, Walter J., "Foreign Governments and Politics," 1927 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Stoezel, Jean, "Recent Progress in the Study of Opinions in Europe," 1947 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Van Riper, Paul Jr., "Civil Service vs. Patronage 1900-1941," 1941 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Henry, "Civilian Advisory Committees Under the National Defense Program," 1941 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Wallette, Hola, "United States Representative Charles C. Diggs Jr.," 1963 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Weaver, Kenneth S., "The Easy Boss," 1952 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Wolfenstein, Victor E., "Some Psychological Aspects of Crisis Leaders," 1966 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Wood, Sally, "An Industrial Eden," 1980 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Zink, "Grand Dragon Stephenson: Political Boss of Indiana," 1959 (Box 64, Folder 14-15)
- Series V: Government Work
  This series contains interviews, memoranda, press releases, and reports from Gosnell's work at the Bureau of the Budget and the Department of State, 1941-1960. This series is organized by department.
  - Bureau of the Budget, data study, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Bureau of the Budget, management bulletin, 1944 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Bureau of the Budget, staff orientation manual, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 3-4)
  - Committee on Foreign Affairs, hearings, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 5-6)
  - Committee on Records of War Administration, memoranda and reports, 1944-1946 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Records of War Administration, report, 1943 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the Study of the Flow of Information and Interdepartmental Relationships, report, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Departments of Commerce and State, fact sheets, 1942-1943 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Department of the Interior, "The Wartime Handling of Evacuee Property," circa 1946 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - "Discussion of Government Security Regulations," 1948 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Division of Field Operations, personnel information, circa 1942 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Division of Statistical Standards, reports, 1942 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - "Domestic Pamphleteers," report, 1944 (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
  - Gosnell, civil service employment application and records, 1941-1958 (Box 66, Folder 8-12)
  - Government and science, reports, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - "Monthly Report on Federal Water Resources," 1939 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - National Emergency Council, reports, 1939-1946 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - National Resources Planning Board, Technicians' Conference, 1938 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - National Resources Planning Board, memoranda and reports, 1940-1941 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - National Resources Planning Board, memoranda and reports, 1940-1941 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - National Resources Planning Board, regional and state plans, 1938 (Box 67, Folder 2-11)
  - Office of the Coordination of Inter-American Affairs, "General Statement," undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Office of Price Administration, consumer information, 1944 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Office of Price Administration, instructions and memoranda, 1941-1943 (Box 68, Folder 3-6)
  - Office of Price Administration, press releases. 1941-1942 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Office of Price Administration, rules, 1941-1942 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Office of War Information, budget, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Office of War Information, interviews, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 10-12)
  - Office of War Information, personnel information, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Office of War Information, personnel information, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Office of War Information, reports, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 2-3)
  - President's Research Committee on Social Trends, report, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - State Department, postwar reconstruction plans, 1941-1944 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - State Department, War History Branch, "Mobilizing for the War of the Worlds," 1946 (Box 69, Folder 6-7)
  - State Department, War History Branch, reports, 1947 (Box 69, Folder 8-10)
  - "The Third International on Its Changes of Policy," confidential report, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - United Front for Better Government Personnel, bulletins, 1930s (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Professional Activities
  This series contains newsletters and some correspondence from organizations to which Gosnell belonged. It is arranged by name and spans 1951-1990.
  - American Association for Public Opinion Research, 1970s-1980s (Box 70, Folder 2-10)
  - American Association for Public Opinion Research, 1970s-1980s (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - American Friends of Captive Nations, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - American Historical Association, 1970s-1980s (Box 71, Folder 5-7)
  - American Political Science Association, 1950s-1980s (Box 71, Folder 8-11)
  - American Political Science Association, 1950s-1980s (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1950s-1980s (Box 72, Folder 3-9)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1950s-1980s (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1950s-1970s (Box 73, Folder 2-6)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1950s-1970s (Box 74, Folder 1-5)
  - Behavioral Research Studies, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
  - Bureau of Social Science Research, 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Citizens Research Foundation, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - The Cosmos Club, 1960s-1980s (Box 75, Folder 1-7)
  - "Current Opinion," 1973 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Election Administration Reports, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Election News, 1972-1974 (Box 76, Folder 1-3)
  - International Society of Political Psychology, 1979-1984 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Social Research, 1971-1982 (Box 76, Folder 5-6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - National Capital Area Political Science Association, 1976-1980 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - National Council on Public Polls, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - National Municipal League, 1961-1980 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - National Opinion Research Center, 1942-1946 (Box 77, Folder 5-8)
  - Oral History Association, 1970s-1980s (Box 77, Folder 9-11)
  - Oral History Association, 1970s-1980s (Box 78, Folder 1-4)
  - Pi Sigma Alpha, 1957-1961 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1965-1983 (Box 78, Folder 6-8)
  - "Political Methodologist," 1989-1990 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Psi Upsilon, 1977-1982 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1943-1946 (Box 79, Folder 2-4)
  - Public Relations Association, 1950s (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Roosevelt Library, 1951 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1935, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1925-1950s (Box 79, Folder 8-10)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1925-1950s (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
  - Society for Social Research, 1930-1940 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Truman Library, 1967-1990 (Box 80, Folder 5-9)
  - Truman Library, 1967-1990 (Box 81, Folder 1-3)
  - The Twentieth Century Fund, 1961-1979 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - United States Information Agency, 1950s-1960s (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
  - Public opinion organizations, circa 1940s-1970s (Box 82, Folder 3-7)
  - Public opinion organizations, circa 1940s-1970s (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
  - World Association for Public Opinion Research, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Series VII: Research Files
  This series contains charts, clippings, interviews, memorabilia, newsletters, notes, publications, polls, propaganda, and surveys related to Gosnell's research on public policy and political theory. Oversized material has been transferred to Series VIII. It is divided into seven subseries:
  Subseries 1: National Elections, contains clippings, newsletters, notes, and propaganda related to presidential and congressional elections between 1926 and 1964. It is organized chronologically.
  Subseries 2: Political Party Ephemera, contains memorabilia, newsletters, and notes related to American party politics between 1928 and 1976. It is organized chronologically.
  Subseries 3: Voting, contains notes, publications, and polls related to voting and electoral behavior. It is organized by topic and spans the 1920s-1960s, though the bulk of the material dates from the 1930s.
  Subseries 4: Public Opinion, contains interviews, notes, polls, publications, and surveys related to measuring public opinion, and its influence on policy. It is organized by research topic and spans the 1910s through the 1977.
  Subseries 5: State and Local Politics, contains charts, clippings, notes, and publications related to state and local politics. It is organized by place and spans the 1920s-1980s, thought the bulk of the material dates from the 1930s.
  Subseries 6: World Politics, contains notes and publications related to the political process outside America. It is organized by place and spans the 1920s through 1970s.
  Subseries 7: General, contains varied research notes on politics and political theory, organized by topic. The bulk of this material is undated, but appears to span Gosnell's academic and political career, from the 1920s through the 1970s.
  - Subseries 1: National Elections
    - Analysis, 1928, 1936-1950 (Box 83, Folder 4-5)
    - Senatorial, 1926 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Presidential, 1936 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Polls, 1940, polls (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Presidential, 1944 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Congressional, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Polls, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Presidential, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Presidential, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
    - Conventions, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Party, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 4-5)
    - Polls, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Presidential and Congressional, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Conventions, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Presidential, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
    - Conventions, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Congressional, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Presidential, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Conventions, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 7-8)
    - Conventions, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Presidential and Congressional, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 2-9)
    - Presidential and Congressional, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 1-5)
  - Subseries 2: Political Party Ephemera
    - Party platforms, 1928-1950 (Box 87, Folder 6-7)
    - Republican Party, Landon campaign, 1936-1943 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Republican Party, 1942-1943 (Box 87, Folder 9-10)
    - Presidential election, 1944 (Box 87, Folder 11-12)
    - Democratic Party, 1946 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1948-1960 (Box 88, Folder 3-4)
    - Young Democrats Club of America, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Republican Party, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Republican National Committee, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Inauguration, 1952 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party, 1954-1956 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Republican Party, 1954-1956 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Campaigns, 1956 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Campaigns, 1956, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
    - Campaigns, 1950s-1960s (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Party, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Campaigns, 1964-1968 (Box 89, Folder 7-9)
    - Conventions and election, 1968, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 1-9)
    - American Party newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Campaign, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Campaign, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Democratic National Committee, undated (Box 91, Folder 2-6)
  - Subseries 3: Voting
    - Absentee voters, 1942 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Ballots, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 92, Folder 1-3)
    - Bureau of the Census data, 1944-1966 (Box 92, Folder 4-5)